http://www.gothfox.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Categories
BurlyCon 2020RhinestonesFeatured Products ...All Products ...
Reviews  [more]
There are currently no product reviews.
Featured  [more]
Wax Pencil$2.00 Sale: $1.70Save: 15% off
Black AB Jelly Rhinestones 20ss - 5 Gross$5.00 Sale: $4.25Save: 15% off
Privacy Notice
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ; To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.gothfox.comVancouver, WAUSAgothfox@speakeasy.netThis policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to Zen desk and save!
Back
Shop
Home
Featured
Specials
New Arrivals
View All
Customer Service
Copyright © 2020 Gothfox Designs.
Powered by Zen Cart.
Responsive Zen cart templates by Picaflor Azul.
Site Map
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Parse Time: 0.194 - Number of Queries: 69 - Query Time: 0.051101081848144
Content
Special Sale ItemsOn sale today!
